Good morning. I have a favor to ask. So the way my page is set up, that people can only comment
if they follow, I am daily amazed at how many Black women are on here talking to me crazy,
but also speaking to me, not as a sister. You know, they can't seem to understand what I'm
saying. So they try to belittle me. They use the same rhetoric as toxically masculine men. I mean,
I tell a story about a policeman abusing his power to give me a compliment and they're not even able
to see that one, someone flashing a badge when you're racing for a flight is not only an abuse
of power, it's highly manipulative and scary, but two, they're so caught up in getting the compliment
and that I should have honored this man giving me the compliment that they don't seem to see how
that man should have honored my time and my consent when I said, I don't have time for this,
but if you'd like to walk with me, you could. I just say all of that to say that
if you are on my page and you are not a sister, would you please unfollow me?
Because I really just want a sisterhood here. And some of y'all really just be sitting around
just to try and comfort me and it's hurtful. So can we just part ways, please?